theory11.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy | theory11

> At THEORY11, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We will never sell or give any of your personal information to anyone. The information we gather is used to provide better service and information to you, our customer.

### Information Collection and Use

THEORY11 collects information from our users on our web site, and is the sole owner of this information. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

### Registration

To place an order on our web site, a user must register by giving their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest.

### Order

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill a customer's order. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the customer.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates until you return to our site. We leave a cookie on the user's machine, which will allow the site to recognize the user when they return. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site, although the user will be limited in some areas of our site.

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic and trending information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services.

We partner with parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

### Links

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we (theory11) are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

### Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. This information is never sold, rented, or leased to third parties, and is kept strictly confidential.

### Surveys & Contests

From time to time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as ZIP code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

### Security

THEORY11 takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When you submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and off-line. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL.

While on a secure page, such as our order form, the padlock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Firefox, Safari, Chrome, and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect customer information off-line.

All of our customers' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific task (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information.

Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, protected by a firewall.Supplementation of InformationIn order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

### Special Offers

We send all new members a welcome email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

### Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from may opt-out of receiving these communications by choosing the un-subscribe option at the bottom of each newsletter.

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties other than those mentioned in this privacy policy above. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

### Site and Service Updates

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

### Correction/Updating Personal Information:

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your ZIP code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the My Account page, or by emailing or calling Customer Support.

### A note about web site errors.

Due to high order volume, an item may go out of stock before we're able to remove it from our site. If this happens, we will notify you personally using the phone number or email address you have provided. Also, although we make every attempt to maintain accuracy, human errors happen from time to time. We cannot honor inaccurate or erroneous price listings. If you see an error, please report it to our support center.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post notification of those changes on our site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
